Alaa Jaradeh

Websites & software developer

Ontario - Canada +1 780-707-2731 info@alaajaradeh.com www.alaajaradeh.com

ABOUT ME

I'am a self-taught OOP PHP developer since 2011 who's always Seeking for the new challenges. Always looking forward to learn more, committed, ambitious and always willing to take the extra mile. A self-motivated, talented web developer with experience in delivering software projects with extremely high standards. A good team player, friendly social active and quick learner.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer — Web developer

Apr 2013 - PRESENT

I started as a web developer career creating websites and online softwares. It gave me a lot of experience and time to learn more technologies.

Sigma Investments LTD, Jordan — *IT Supervisor*

Apr 2012 - Mar 2015

The IT department was my responsibility since i joined the

- I was responsible about website development, maintenance, updates and the used technologies
- Developed many inhouse softwares for departments and CRM
- Servers ,Clouds and domains purchase, maintenance, control and development.
- SEO and online campaigns

SIT-MENA, Jordan— Web developer

Jan 2011- Feb 2012

Semantic Intelligent Technologies is a technology house company where we were responsible of development softwares and websites.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

* PHP MVC Frameworks

- Yii2.
- Zend Framework
- Zend Framework 2
- Codeigniter

* PHP CMS Frameworks

- Drupal
- Joomla
- Wordpress

* Ecommerce Platform

- Magento
- OpenCart
- WooCommerce

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- EC2/EC3 Amazon
- Cloud Server
- WHM/cPanel
- Windows Serve
- Github
- Bitbucket
- JIRA
- IDE
- CS5/CS6/CC
- UI/UX
- Social media API

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Ability to multi-task, react quickly to shifting priorities and meet deadlines
- Proactive, confident and with a positive "can-do" attitude.
- Able to clearly communicate technical data to non technical colleagues and clients
- Continuously monitoring industry trends, technologies and standards
- Possessing all-round analysis and programming skills
- Methodical yet creative & having a proven ability for efficient problem solving
- Excellent attention to details both front and backend
- Able to write a clean documented code
- Solid web development experience using OOP, PHP, AJAX, MySQL, JavaScript, Jquery, XML, REST/SOAP APIS, GIT, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Quds College, Jordan — Diploma Degree

Apr 2015

Computer Information System (CIS).

Is a plus I got the highest CIS degree in that year.

New English Schools, $Jordan-High\ school$

2008

LANGUAGES

- Arabic (mother tongue language)
- English (fluent)